firsttrustbank.co.uk 2012-06-29

# First Trust Personal Finance - Work & Money

## Your Right to Privacy

You have a right to know how we (AIB Group (UK) p.l.c.) will use your personal information.  It is important to read the following Collection, SWIFT Payments and Use of Technical Information sections.

Please note that references to “we” means AIB Group (UK) p.l.c. Trading as First Trust Bank and our subsidiaries and associates.

Where reference to ‘AIB Group’ is made, this means Allied Irish Banks, p.l.c., its subsidiaries and associates.  This includes AIB Group (UK) p.l.c.

#### Collection and Use of Information  

  * We will not collect any personal information about you on this website without your consent. We will let you know what we intend doing with your information before collecting it, so that you can decide whether or not to furnish that information to us. For more information on how we use cookies on this website, view our 'Using Cookies' page.
  * Any information, which is provided by you, will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality and in accordance with current Data Protection legislation and regulation.
  * If at any time after giving us personal information you decide that you no longer wish us to hold or use this information, or in the case that the information becomes out of date, you are free to notify us, and we will remove or rectify the information within a reasonable time and in accordance with legislative requirements.
  * You acknowledge and agree that in certain circumstances we may be obliged to disclose personal information relating to you to third parties, for example, in order to conform to any requirements of law or to comply with any legal process, as well as to protect and defend our rights or property, and that of our licensors and/or our other customers.
  * Telephone calls may be monitored or recorded to ensure that we carry out your instructions correctly and to help improve the quality of our service and in the interests of security.

Should you have any queries in relation to how we handle your personal information you can contact us at AIB Group (UK) p.l.c. First Trust Centre, 92 Ann Street, Belfast, BT1 3HH  

#### Swift Payments

International payments and certain domestic payments are made by us via the Belguim based **Society for World Interbank Financial Telecommunication** ("SWIFT"). SWIFT processes these types of payments on behalf of financial institutions worldwide and is currently the only organisation providing such a service. Records of all transactions processed by SWIFT in Belgium are replicated in a backup system ("mirror site") in the US, thereby maintaining a geographically separated back-up infrastructure to ensure that the continued operation of the SWIFT system is in line with international standards and supervisory requirements.

On foot of US legal subpoena(s) served on SWIFT, transaction data held in the US "mirror site" may be disclosed to the US government, its various departments and agencies (including law enforcement), or other national, state or international authorities for the purposes of combating terrorism and other serious crime.

Therefore, any information you provide to us in order to effect a SWIFT payment could potentially be disclosed to US authorities, and by instructing us to execute a payment, you are implicitly giving your consent to such disclosure and agree that we shall have no liability to you in respect of any such disclosure.

We reserve the right to amend this notice at any time, and you should regularly check for any amendments.

#### Use of Technical Information

Cookies are files which are transferred to your computer’s hard disk by a website. Cookies can store information about your preferences and other information, which you need when you visit a website.  We use cookies to monitor our website traffic, to ensure better service levels and in order to provide you with certain features such as the customised delivery of certain information. To prevent the use of cookies you should activate the facility which is available in most web browsers that enables a user to deny or accept cookies. Find out how to enable/disable cookies in our Related Information section.

Statistical and analytical information collected through the standard operation of our Internet servers and logs provides us with general and not individually specific information. We will make no attempt to identify individual users, or to associate any technical information collected with any individual user.

####   
Disclaimer  

We, our directors, employees, servants and agents, affiliates or other representatives and our respective parent and subsidiary companies, shall not be liable in respect of any claims, emergencies, demands, causes of action, damages, losses, expenses, including without limitation, reasonable legal fees and costs of proceedings arising out of or in connection with the use and/or dissemination of personal information relating to you in accordance with this privacy policy and your consents.

You should be aware that where you link to another website from our website that we have no control over that other website.  We have no responsibility for the privacy practices of other websites.

#### Amendments

We reserve the right in our sole discretion to amend this privacy statement at any time, and you should regularly check this privacy statement for any amendments **.**

Back to top
